[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "Has he ever been in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "How do you feel about being called a genius?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "I'm a fairly peaceful, docile individual.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "You were how old when you did these draws?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "It's funny, I have no recollection of doing that so probably two or three years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Shaquille O'Neal"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What is she doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "She's ready to make Shaquille O'Neal's day, it looks like.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "At what point did you go from gentle cartoonist to an evil person?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Probably about four, I guess.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "You see the absurd and slightly sinister in everything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "The absurd, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry", "Michele Bachmann"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Are you thrilled because it gives you great material?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I guess with a Rick Perry or a Michele Bachmann it would be the best possible thing to happen to comedy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Is that the dream double ticket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Probably, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2011"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Do you fundamentally like their policies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "In 2011, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Can you tell me who that is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Stewie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "It's the basic math adds up, it adds up, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I just screwed up your card.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Do you think that Obama can win the next election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "No idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "What's the left-wing equivalent of the tea party, would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "I struggle to find one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "That's what I'm told.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "When you watch that, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Not very proper.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Have you always had an absolutely clear idea of what you were going to do in animated form?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$100 million"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Your contract is believed to be over $100 million.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Are any of these allegations true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "I guess if it's believed to be so that makes it true in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Was that a denial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Yes, that's what my lawyers tell me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Are you motivated by it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "If there's a Republican president, I will just keep getting richer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Taylor Lautner"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 205, "question": "You have a problem getting a girl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Look, if I was, you know, Taylor Lautner walking around, I would have --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "How many times have you been turned down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "As much as the next guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Is it the lines you're using?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Maybe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Can I say that on CNN?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "You just did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "How did do you that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Well, I was animation major in college.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "You didn't know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Your mother broke it to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "How did you react?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "ACFARLANE: My mother was always the first person to know gossip.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "How important was she to your career?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Really, really -- certainly from a comedy standpoint, you know, just invaluable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "There is not a mother in the world that would not be offended by something that you have done and you're sitting here telling me that your mother went along with all of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Yes, she was unflappable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Do you have any lines?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Yes, there are some things off limits.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Well, we wouldn't make a -- we wouldn't make a 9/11 joke for at least two weeks after 9/11.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "And how far do you tread?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "That is just your gut.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Is religion a particularly sensitive issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "ETER: Oh, so Saddam Hussein did this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Saddam Hussein"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "The Iraqi Army?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraqi Army"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Some guys from Iraq?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Peter"], "LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "That one lady who visited Iraq that one time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "No, Peter, Iraq had nothing to do with this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "A combination of two things: I was -- I was giving a lecture at my college the night before, and went out with some of the faculty afterwards and had a few pints.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Does any part of you shudder at your own shocking humor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "CD", "VBD", "RB", ":", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Which has been your favorite, because you've done a few now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "This last one was pretty -- was -- I mean, it was -- it was dark, but it was definitely fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "What do you -- what do you make of Charlie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "You know, it's funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "How would you feel if a member of Amy Winehouse's family watching that was really upset and actually phoned you to say, what were you doing making jokes about Amy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Well, what I would say was that the joke was about Charlie.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy Winehouse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", ":", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Would you be uncomfortable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "The part that -- I -- oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Have you had those calls?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Not -- no, I actually haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Well, how do you know about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "It's a great story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "How did you find out about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Never mind how I know these things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Did you -- did you grovel pathetically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Stand your ground like a man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I tried.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "I mean, there's a certain irony in Jon Stewart ringing up, haranguing you for mocking him, isn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I mean, it's -- if I say yes, he's going to crucify me on his show every night for a year.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon Stewart"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Wrong to not see the funny side?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What are you schizophrenic, or what is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "ORGAN: I heard this, his original one, yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Isn't that the next obvious step?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I have -- I enjoy many different pursuits.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "How about the new Morey Amsterdam?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "But, finally, I'm told that you had a very exciting new addition to your \"Family Guy\" cast list.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Morey Amsterdam"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", ":", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Is this right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Yes, it turns out -- yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "''", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "What should people know about this guy from Wales?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "I'm 6'4\".", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wales"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Simon"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Everyone is thinking who are -- how did Steve Jones get to be the host of the hottest new show on TV in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "WP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Well, Simon had approached me about four years ago to work on a project which I couldn't do because I was under contract with a different channel.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jones"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Two years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "About two years ago, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "he needs nipping in the bud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "I'm just going to do the best I can do on the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "What was that picture that just came up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "Let's rewind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "What was that picture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "What a little nerd.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "What's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "That is me as a child in my bathers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Do you still wear those?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "That reminds me of a story my mother used to tell ex- girlfriends when I used to take them to meet my mother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "Talking about that particular part of your anatomy, do you still have a plaster cast of it on your mantle piece at home in Wales?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "It's not on the mantle piece.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wales"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "They must be crawling around Sunset Boulevard, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "Well -- I'll be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sunset Boulevard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "Is it all you hoped it would be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Yes, and more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Was it true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "She's a good friend of mine, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Hayden Panettiere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "She's a friend of mine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "Halle Barry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "ONES: I interviewed her once.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Halle Barry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jones", "Steve Jones"]}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "You're happy with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "Yes, I think there will be a lot of people not be asking who is Steve Jones, but, whoa, Steve Jones.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Can I ask you a huge favor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111006pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Can I storm off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]